

CONTACT



Kyiv, Ukraine



borrline@gmail.com



git https://github.com/Yborline



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ yaroslav-borys-793268231/



+38(095)-602-53-85

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript ES6+ React Svelte Redux GitHub Next **Handlebars** Node.js REST API TypeScript

Figma framer-motion WebPack. Parcel @react-oauth/google

bootstrap yup dayjs i18next

HTML5/CSS3/SASS/BEM

SOFT SKILLS

- Ability to work under pressure
- Conscientious
- Bussiness communication skills
- Responsible
- Creative
- Easy learner
- Honest
- Result-oriented
- Accurate
- Flexible

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian native
- Russian fluent
- English intermediate

YAROSLAV BORYS

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

My new passion is creating and learning websites. That is why I am interested in the position of Front-End Developer. I have knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. During my studies, I worked on several projects (you can see my GitHub account). I am a fast learner and am ready for challenging tasks. I will be glad to become a part of big and interesting projects. My goal is to enjoy mv work.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

♣ All projects are here ◆ https://new-resume-two.vercel.app/projects

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Frontend developer

Liberty 2023 - Present

Development of various tasks, creation of game menus, administrative tickets from users, creation of game quests, many game pages, a lot of logic in all tasks and also work with the client of the GTA5 game itself

Trainee Frontend developer

Prosperity Business Assistant 2023 Development of single-page sites

Sales manager

Mobile Trand | 2021 - 2022 |

Sales; fulfillment of the assigned tasks from the office; control over all changes in the company.

Head of warehouse

MK (Private company) 2018-2021

Organization of the work of the warehouse; analysis of orders and the formation of applications; even distribution of work among all employees. Reached the highest level of career growth in this company.

EDUCATION

State University of Infrastructure and Technologies

| 2018 - 2021 |

Faculty of transport technologies on railway transport

Kyiv Professional College of Transport Infrastructure

| 2014 - 2018 |- with honours

Faculty of organization of transportation and management of railway transport

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

IT School GoIT

12021-2022 |

Full Stack Developer

Children's Music School Nº14 them. D. Kabalevsky

| 2006 - 2014 |

Violin, piano